admanmedia.com 2013-04-30

# ADman Media . Privacy

## Privacy and personal data protection policy

Please spend a few minutes reading our Privacy Policy and familiarizing yourself with the measures that we take to protect your personal data. You are hereby informed that this Privacy Policy forms part of the General Terms of Use for ADmanMedia. By using ADmanMedia, you are accepting this Privacy Policy and providing your express and unequivocal consent for your personal data to be processed under the terms specified below. You can view these terms at any time on our website. 

### ADman Media user

ADmanMedia is an application that enables you to publish ads via your social media sites in exchange for a payment that will be calculated based on the results obtained (for publishing, for visiting, for registration, for purchase or based on any other medium defined in the future). 

To become an ADman Media user and be able to benefit from all the advantages of ADmanMedia, you must be over 18 years old and have the legal capacity to enter into a contract, bind yourself and complete the corresponding registration form. All fields on the registration form must be filled out to complete registration. 

ADmanMedia has an area reserved for its registered users, which you will be able to access once the registration process is complete. Only registered users have access to this area. 

As an ADmanMedia user, you must notify us of any changes in the data you have provided to us. In any event, you are responsible for the truthfulness and accuracy of the data provided at all times. However, notwithstanding any other action to which it may be entitled, ADmanMedia reserves the right to refuse to register or to cancel the account of any user who provides false or incomplete data. 

### Processing personal data

In accordance with Organic Law 15/1999, on Personal Data Protection, ADmanMedia shall undertake to maintain the privacy of any data you expressly consent to share with us. This data will be added to the relevant electronic data file for processing, owned and held by ADMAN INTERACTIVE, S.L. with a registered office at C/ Llacuna, 162-164 08018 Barcelona. The purpose of collecting and processing your personal data is to: 

  * Identify you as a user, assist you in managing your account and handle any relevant payments.
  * Provide and offer our services to you.
  * Send update notifications for products and services.
  * Monitor and track the results obtained by the user through the IP and ADman program installed.
  * Administration, billing and user management.
  * Surveys, statistics and profile analysis.

In order to provide the service to our users, the personal data supplied when registering will also be sent (via international data transfer) to the company Addap, Inc, with a registered office at 2200 Western Avenue, Seattle, WA 98121 (United States). The purpose of this is to enable us to offer the service, monitor and track the results obtained by the user and make the corresponding payment to the user. 

In addition, provided that you authorize us to do so by clicking on the corresponding section of the form, we can use your data to send you any type of advertising information related to ADmanMedia’s business activities and the products and services that we offer through ADmanMedia to the email address provided. 

ADmanMedia has adopted the levels of security for personal data protection required by law, and has installed all resources and technical measures available to prevent the loss, misuse, modification, unauthorized access and theft of personal data provided. Nonetheless, you must be aware that security measures on the Internet are not impregnable. 

ADmanMedia will not transfer your personal data to third parties without obtaining your consent by informing you in advance of the identity of the recipient and the purpose of the transfer of your personal data. Nonetheless, you are giving us express authorization to use your data and make it available to our providers or agents in the event that you present any question or complaint regarding the services and products offered by us and/or our providers or agents, for the sole purpose of investigating your questions and/or complaints. 

ADmanMedia reserves the right to request your personal ID card number or even a copy of the document in order to verify the data in your account. 

At any time, you may exercise your rights of access, correction, cancellation or opposition by sending a signed written request, accompanied by a copy of your ID card or other valid identification document, to: ADMAN INTERACTIVE, S.L, C/ Llacuna, 162-164 08018 Barcelona; or by emailing these to [baja@admanmedia.com](mailto:baja@admanmedia.com "baja@admanmedia.com")

In addition, registered users may complete or modify their personal data by using the tools set up for this purpose in the user account area. 

### Personal data and payment of balances

In order to request payment of your balance, you must complete the full user profile, which you will have access to once you have completed your ADmanMedia registration. 

There are two payment methods for income generated through use of ADmanMedia services: bank transfer and/or PayPal. 

If payment is made via PayPal, your bank account information is collected, stored and handled by PayPal as the payment entity responsible for managing and paying the balance accrued in your account. 

In this case, you must comply with PayPal’s [Privacy Policy](https://cms.paypal.com/en/cgi-bin/?&cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_EN "Política de Privacidad") and [Terms of Use](https://cms.paypal.com/en/cgi-bin/?&cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/UserAgreement_full&locale.x=en_EN "Condiciones de uso"). 

### Cancelling your ADmanMedia account

To cancel your ADmanMedia account, all you need to do is send an email to [baja@ADmanMedia.com](mailto:baja@ADmanMedia.com "baja@ADmanMedia.com") asking us to remove you.  
You are hereby informed that if you cancel your ADmanMedia account, you will be unable to access your account again and you will lose all personal information stored. 

For any questions you may have, you may contact us by sending an email to our customer service department at [ayuda@ADmanMedia.com](mailto:ayuda@ADmanMedia.com "ayuda@ADmanMedia.com")

### Cookies

ADmanMedia can install “cookies” on your computer’s hard drive to register your visit. 

A cookie is a small, anonymous data packet sent to your browser from our website and/or application. This information is stored on your computer’s hard drive. ADmanMedia can use the information from the cookie to remember your username and password when you return to the site and/or application. This means that you do not have to log in again, providing a more satisfactory experience. 

You can configure your browser to reject cookies. However, if you do so, you will have to identify yourself every time you use ADmanMedia in order to publish the promotions we offer you. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Should any changes be made to our privacy practices and/or policy in the future that may affect your personal data, we will inform you of the relevant changes through our website. These changes will be valid from the time they are announced. We therefore encourage you to review our Privacy Policy frequently.
